本故事纯属虚构。作品中出现的人名、地名及团体名等均与现实没有任何关系。
金华山 黄金山神社
金华山
三陆复兴
国立公园
This is a work of fiction. The names of the people, places, and organizations
are fictitious and in no way related to any real person or entity.
10 Minutes Later
Number 12
Psssssszzzzzzzzz
Hokkaido
Notsuke Peninsula
Shiretoko Mountain Range
Hokkaido
Notsuke Peninsula
Mount Rausu
MY DEER FRIEND NOKOTAN
RUNNING BEGINS
Clueless Yet Again
Nekoyamada Neko-san (3rd-Year)
UNEXPECTED VISITORS
RUN
THE PURSUER
THE PURSUED
Principal's Office
Every Miller Draws Water to His Own Mill
NOKOTAN'S IN DIRE STRAITS
This is my rifle.
There are many like it, but this one is mine.
My rifle is my best friend. It is my life.
I must master it as
I must master my life.
My rifle
and myself are the defenders of my country.
We are the masters of our enemy.
We are the saviors of my life.
Friendship
Effort
Victory
When carrying or transporting a firearm,
said firearm must be placed in a container.
(Excerpt from the Firearm and Sword Possession Control Law)
Hokkaido
Nemuro Strait
Stream
Deer
Crackers
One Hour Ago
Deer
Crackers
NB: Nokotan
Rip
Deer Club
Seeking New Club Members