本故事纯属虚构。作品中出现的人名、地名及团体名等均与现实没有任何关系。
金华山 黄金山神社
金华山
三陆复兴
国立公园
This is a work of fiction. The names of the people, places, and organizations
are fictitious and in no way related to any real person or entity.
Deer Club
Seeking New Club Members
Deer Crackers
Blame It on the Spring
Student Council
Deer Club
Seeking New Club Members
Hino Zoo
Hino Veterinary Hospital for Doggies and Kitties
Izu Peninsula
Hachijo-jima
Reeves's muntjacs
Deer Club
Seeking New Club Members
Deer Crackers
Flower Arrangement Club
The Next Day
Deer Club
Seeking New Club Members
A very cute
Reeves's muntjac
from Hachijo-jima
Deer Crackers
Deer Club
Seeking New Club Members